I get so angry that people don't care more about other people.
At a certain point, it has to stop being about just you and your stuff and your house and your kids.
You have to care about the greater good.
Because if you don't care about climate change, where are your babies going to live?
Because it's going to keep getting hotter.
You okay with your grandbabies on fire?
Apparently they are.
Yeah.
I don't understand this.
It's why is money more important than people?
Profits over people.
Power over people.
That's not how it's supposed to be.
We're supposed to care about each other and help each other, even sacrificially.
Like going back to the school board votes.
Yes, take more of my taxes if it's going to help these babies learn what they need to learn.
Yeah.
What's wrong with that?
How much money do you need?
I feel like there's just a real disconnect from what you said in terms of like, we should be caring about people, right?
The human inhumanity is lost.
Absolutely.